Fraser Valley University Society fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Board, committee and meeting records, 1990 - 1998; F-171-4; 38 cm of textual records
  - Minutes, correspondence and supporting papers, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 171-10)
  - Minutes, correspondence and supporting papers, vol. 3, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 171-10)
  - Minutes, correspondence and supporting papers, vol. 4, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 171-10)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy, Executive and Advisory Committees, vol. 1, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 171-10)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy, Executive and Advisory Committees, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 171-10)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy, Executive and Advisory Committees, vol. 3, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 171-10)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy, Executive and Advisory Committees, vol. 4, 1990 - 1991; F-171-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy and Fundraising Committees, vol. 1, 1990 - 1993; F-171-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy and Fundraising Committees, vol. 2, 1990 - 1993; F-171-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy and Fundraising Committees, vol. 3, 1990 - 1993; F-171-4-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy and Fundraising Committees, vol. 4, 1990 - 1993; F-171-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors, Strategy and Fundraising Committees, vol. 5, 1990 - 1993; F-171-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - miscellaneous committee and meeting, vol. 1, 1991 - 1992; F-171-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - miscellaneous committee and meeting, vol. 2, 1991 - 1992; F-171-4-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
  - Minutes - miscellaneous committee and meeting, vol. 3, 1991 - 1992; F-171-4-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 171-11)
- Community relations, promotion and fundraising records, 1990 - 1998; F-171-5; 63 cm of textual records 25 photographs 27 slides 15 negatives 3 moving images; Physical description: moving images consist of 4 videocassettes that have been digitized as .mov preservation and .mp4 access copies. General note: photographs are located in files F-171-5-0-0-6.1 (5 photos), F-171-5-0-0-13.1 (6 photos), F-171-5-0-0-80.1 (14 photos).
  Series consists of records relating to the community relations, promotion and fundraising activities of the Fraser Valley University Society and the Technical University of British Columbia.
  Specific activities, events and topics documented include publicity and advertising, media relations, community outreach, speeches and talks, fundraising events, donor relations and committee meetings and reports, particularly of the Fundraising, Community Relations, and Public Relations Committees.
  Records include newspaper articles, press releases and related records, correspondence, newsletters, brochures, flyers, invitations, speeches, lists, video cassettes, photographs, slides, and drawings.
  The arrangement was provided by the archivist. News articles were originally housed in binders, and are divided according to month or geographical area by the creator.
  Records relating to the meetings and activities of this committee may also be found in the following series: Board, committee and meeting records.
  - Delta Council and Alex Soroka's presentation - resolution passed, June 1991; F-171-5-0-0-0-1; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2373)
    Soroka, Alex; Corporation of Delta; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .mov file also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-171-item4.
    - OBJ-2373-dgt.mov
  - Presentation tape: UTV, Karen Yong and Dr. Saywell, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-0-2; 2 videocassettes 2 .mov files (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2374, Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2375)
    Yong, Karen; Saywell, William George; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Open
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-171-item1, F-171-item2.
    - OBJ-2374-dgt.mov
    - OBJ-2375-dgt.mov
  - Fraser Valley University Society presentation, September 1994; F-171-5-0-0-0-3; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2376)
    Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-171-item3.
    - OBJ-2376-dgt.mov
  - Brochures - historical, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Brochures - original, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Community relations - pledge forms - directors, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Community relations - presentations, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Community relations - letters of introduction, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Community relations - newsletter, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Community relations - Semiahmoo Mall (photographs), February 1992; F-171-5-0-0-6.1; Physical description: 5 photographs. (Archival box - small 171-20)
    Photographic materials
  - Community relations - volunteer meeting minutes, 1991; F-171-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Promotional correspondence, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Administration - letters of parents - school notices, 1993; F-171-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Donation requests, 1997; F-171-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Donor thanks, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Donors, 1991 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
    Restricted in whole
  - Fashion show 1992, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fashion Show 1992 (photographs), F-171-5-0-0-13.1; Physical description: 6 photographs and 1 newspaper article. (Archival box - small 171-20)
  - Fashion show October 7, 1993, vol. 1, F-171-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fashion show October 7, 1993, vol. 2, F-171-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising, 1991; F-171-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising, 1991 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising - auction items (live), 1991 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising - banquet/auction May 1994, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising - banquet ticket inventory, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising - casino application, 1995 - 1996; F-171-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 171-12)
  - Fundraising - choir ticket inventory, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - minutes of meetings, 1994; F-171-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising committee, vol. 1, 1994 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising committee, vol. 2, 1994 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising committee, vol. 3, 1994 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - computer show information, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - contacts (out), 1992; F-171-5-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - correspondence, 1993 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - correspondence - donation letter, 1994; F-171-5-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - dinner, 1991; F-171-5-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - donors (past), 1995; F-171-5-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - Excel, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - grants, research, follow-up, 1992 - 1993; F-171-5-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - ideas, 1992 - 1993; F-171-5-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - Jubilations - dinner and theatre, 1995; F-171-5-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - root beer float, vol. 1, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - root beer float, vol. 2, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - Summit Communications, 1991; F-171-5-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - A Taste of the Fraser Valley, 1994 fundraiser, 1993 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Fundraising - Welsh Men's Choir, April 4, 1992, F-171-5-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 171-13)
  - Golf tournament, June 1996, 1996 - 1997; F-171-5-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - Interviews, 1991 - 1996; F-171-5-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - Logos, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-44
  - Media releases, 1991 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - Media - magazine articles, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 1, 1990 - 1991; F-171-5-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-171-5-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 3, 1990 - 1991; F-171-5-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 4, 1990 - 1991; F-171-5-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 5, 1990 - 1991; F-171-5-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 6, 1990 - 1991; F-171-5-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles - Richmond, Surrey/N. Delta, Vancouver, White Rock, other, vol. 1, 1990 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles - Richmond, Surrey/N. Delta, Vancouver, White Rock, other, vol. 2, 1990 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles - Richmond, Surrey/N. Delta, Vancouver, White Rock, other, vol. 3, 1990 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 1, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 171-14)
  - News articles, vol. 2, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - News articles, vol. 1, 1992 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - News articles, vol. 2, 1992 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - News articles, vol. 3, 1992 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - News articles, vol. 4, 1992 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - News articles, vol. 5, 1992 - 1995; F-171-5-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Newsletters, 1991 - 1997; F-171-5-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Newsletter - Tech BC, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Presentation slides: "A degree granting University is needed in the Fraser Valley", 1993; F-171-5-0-0-65.1; Physical description: 27 slides. (Archival box - small 171-20)
  - Presentation sheets, 1992; F-171-5-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Press releases, vol. 1, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Press releases, vol. 2, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 171-15)
  - Press releases, vol. 3, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Press releases, vol. 4, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Press releases, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Promotional material, 1991 - 1996; F-171-5-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Promotional material and community relations and fundraising report, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Public relations, 1991 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Public relations - media, 1992 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Publicity - correspondence, 1994; F-171-5-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Publicity - media contact list, 1990 - 1992; F-171-5-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Ribbon-cutting ceremony - October 9, 1991, F-171-5-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Roger's Cable information, 1991 - 1994; F-171-5-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Speaker's program, 1996; F-171-5-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Talk and fundraising events photographs, 1991; F-171-5-0-0-80.1; Physical description: 14 photographs and 15 negatives. (Archival box - small 171-20)
  - Tech BC brochure, 1998; F-171-5-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
- Government relations records, 1989 - 1995; F-171-6; 10 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the society's relations and correspondence with government bodies and individuals involved in government affairs, particularly at the municipal and provincial level. Includes records relating to the activities of the Governent Relations Committee, as well as the Interim Planning Committee established by the Provincial Government in 1994 to assist in the establishment of the Technical University of British Columbia. Series also includes records concerning government organization and education policies and campaigns, accumulated by the society for informational purposes.
  Records include correspondence, reports, minutes, press releases and newspaper articles.
  - Government relations - Advanced Education, Ministry of - press releases, 1992; F-171-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Government relations - correspondence, vol. 1, 1990 - 1995; F-171-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 171-16)
  - Government relations - correspondence, vol. 2, 1990 - 1995; F-171-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Government - government, October 1991-1996, 1989 - 1991; F-171-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Administration - government - Fraser Valley Committee on Post-Ed (M. Neylan), 1992; F-171-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Government relations - government appointment information, 1990 - 1993; F-171-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Government relations - news articles, 1993; F-171-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Government relations - planning council, 1994; F-171-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Government relations - planning council information documents, 1995; F-171-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Government relations - reports, 1993; F-171-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Administration - G.V.R.D., 1991 - 1992; F-171-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Institution and government report, 1991 - 1993; F-171-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Ministry of Advanced Education, Technology and Training, 1991 - 1993; F-171-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - MLA - minutes of meeting, 1991 - 1992; F-171-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - MLA - updates, 1991 - 1992; F-171-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Provincial government - Premier, 1991 - 1992; F-171-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
- Membership records, 1990 - 1997; F-171-7; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records petaining to society membership. Donor lists are sometimes included in files with member lists.
  Records include policies and procedures, forms and membership lists.
  - Administration - membership processing procedures, 1991; F-171-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Membership card, 1991; F-171-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Administration - membership - renewal forms, 1993; F-171-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Membership renewal requests, 1997; F-171-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Mailing lists, 1990 - 1991; F-171-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Members - past, 1993 - 1994; F-171-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Past memberships, 1995 - 1996; F-171-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
  - Memberships, donors, supporters, 1997; F-171-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 171-17)
- Reports and reference files, 1983 - 1997; F-171-8; 24 cm of textual records; Records date predominantly between 1989 and [1997?].
  Series consists of reports by and relating to the society, as well as reports, news releases, statistics and other material used by the society to research post-secondary education in British Columbia. Series also include reports by and relating to the Fraser Valley Access Committee, the Fraser Valley Committee on Post-Secondary Education, the Technical University of British Columbia Interim Planning Council and the Technical University of British Columbia.
  - Administration - Kwantlen University College, 1990; F-171-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Administration - post-secondary ed. priorities, NDP, 1990; F-171-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Administration - research, 1991 - 1992; F-171-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Administration - survey to teachers / administrators, 1995; F-171-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Report of the Fraser Valley Committee on Post-Secondary Education, phase I, June 1993; F-171-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Fraser Valley Real Estate Board, 1996; F-171-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Proposals - job development training program, 1991 - 1992; F-171-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Proposals - rise project #1, 1992; F-171-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - Advanced Education, Ministry of - access for all, 1989 - 1993; F-171-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - B.C. post-secondary education, 1990 - 1991; F-171-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - Douglas College, 1990; F-171-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - F.V.A.C.-related reports, vol. 1, 1989 - 1991; F-171-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - F.V.A.C.-related reports, vol. 2, 1989 - 1991; F-171-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - F.V.A.C.-related reports, vol. 3, 1989 - 1991; F-171-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - F.V.A.C.-related reports, vol. 4, 1989 - 1991; F-171-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 171-18)
  - Research - F.V.A.C.-related reports and minutes, 1991 - 1995; F-171-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research / data - F.V.U.S., 1990 - 1992; F-171-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Fraser Valley University Society, 1991; F-171-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research - Kwantlen College - statistics, vol. 1, 1990 - 1993; F-171-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research - Kwantlen College - statistics, vol. 2, 1990 - 1993; F-171-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research - research completed, 1992; F-171-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research - Simon Fraser University, 1983 - 1991; F-171-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research - statistics, 1990 - [ca 1992]; F-171-8-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Research - University College of the Fraser Valley, 1990; F-171-8-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Technical University of B.C. - Interim Planning Council draft, June 1996; F-171-8-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 171-19)
  - Technical University of B.C., 1997; F-171-8-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 171-19)